and our notes about this.
All you need to do is mark out the previous day high
and the previous day low.
Now once that occurs,
now what I mean by break above the high or the low
is basically we're sweeping above the high
or below the low.
Now what I mean by sweep is that all you do is break
above that pivotal key zone,
or you break below that pivotal key zone.
You've noticed that has occurred at a higher time frame.
Stop looking at the fucking NASDAQ.
This is for the NASDAQ only, right?
What you're gonna do is you're gonna follow the fucking money.
Now the NASDAQ is the [index-company description unclear in audio] companies.
I could have saved here and watched 100 fucking
nine financial companies.
I'm gonna watch the Magnificent Seven,
the companies that moved the market
because of the highest market caps.
Within the market they got a lot of fucking money,
a lot of vitality.
See majority of those assets are buying.
I should not be fucking shorting.
I should be looking for a long position.
See majority of those assets selling.
I should not be looking for a long.
I should be shorting that fucking shit.
If I see those assets are mismatch,
some are up, some are down, some are out supply,
some are out demand, support resistance,
whatever the fucking case scenario may be.
I turned the fucking charts off [unclear linking words] evidence
of confirmation before clicking any fucking button.
Where is if the NASDAQ breaks above
our sweeps above the key level, pivotal zone?
The MAGS-7 is doing what I wanted to do
and following the money.
Then I would look at the VIX, right?
The V-I-X, the vitality, all right?
Listen up, write this shit fucking down.
As soon as I think that I want a short position,
the VIX better be buying, but not just randomly buying.
It better be buying off demand.
And if I'm doing to do the opposite,
it best be doing the opposite.
If you catch my driftin', if you know what I mean.